# MIGUELMARCO RAMCHARAN

## SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

#### CONTACT

061 149 8474

miguelmarcoramcharan@gmail.com

https://www.codebymarco.com

Durban, South Africa

\_\_\_\_\_

### SKILLS

- HTML5
- CSS
- TYPESCRIPT
- NODEJS
- GOLANG
- SQL
- NOSQL
- POSTGRES
- RABBITMQ
- JENKINS
- KUBERNETES
- DOCKER
- AWS/GCP
- DEVOPS

\_\_\_\_\_

#### EDUCATION

**High School Diploma** 

## Rydalpark Secondary

2012-2016

Completed my matric ant my local high school

\_\_\_\_\_

### HOBBIES

- FOOTBALL
- LEARNING ABOUT THE UNIVERSE
- WATCHING HISTORY DOCUMENTARYS
- CODING
- RELAXING

### PROFILE

I'm a self-taught software developer with 2 years of experience. After high school, I found myself working in my dad's carpentry business, but I realized coding was my true passion. I learned through countless YouTube tutorials and Codecademy, and I got my first job on my very first application. I have learnt alot over the last 2 years and look foward to what my future in tech has in store for me. I love using technology to create exciting things on the web.

### WORK EXPERIENCE

### Carpenter

El-Shaddai Interiors

2017-2022

I stared working here after i compeletd my matric. I was tasked with checking the materials that arrived on site, assembling, fitting and finsishing the final product

## **Software Developer**

Decidio 2023- present

I was initially brought on to work as a support agent on the TRUENDO product and was then pushed to a develop role .

My tasks involved

- finding bugs and fixing them
- implementing new features
- optimization of the product
- Developer operations

## PROJECT LINKS

- https://indeed-console.vercel.app
- https://iportfolio-console.vercel.app
- https://formio-console.vercel.app
- https://linkbio-console.vercel.app